Today I reached home from office crying.
Before that, I woke up in the morning, took a bath, got
ready quickly and left for office.  As soon as I
reached the office, avoiding the sun, I first
met my friend and started the day by
looking at myself in the mirror and decided that the day went well.
Then like him, I got busy with my work.  Before I knew it, it was
lunch time and I was
very hungry.  The weather was
so lovely but little did I
know that I would cry by the time I reached home.
Suddenly my leg got twisted and the pain was so much that I can't even
describe it.  Mom became even
more tense.  Without wasting time, I
quickly went to get it checked.  I thought
maybe I would find Ram after getting a massage etc.
But the pain is getting worse.
Then I came home and bandaged it etc.
Mom brought food but I didn't feel like eating it at all.